<all>
	<unit>
		<theory>
Adverb:
1. To, from, or at a considerable distance: a cat that had strayed far from home.
2. To, from, or at a much earlier or later time: a movie that takes place far in the future.
3. To a considerable degree; much: felt far better yesterday; eyes that seemed far too close together.
4. To an advanced point or stage: a brilliant student who will go far.

Adjectives:
 Being at considerable distance (far, distant, remote): a far country.
 Going back a considerable extent in time (far, far-off, distant): far-off future, distant past.
 Coming from or going to a distance (distant): a distant sound; a distant telephone call.
 More distant than another (usually of two things) (far). He lives on the far side of the lake.: the far corner.
 Extensive or lengthy (far): a far journey
 Distantly related by blood or marriage (distant): distant cousin.
 Minimally similar (distant): a distant likeness.
 Operating or controlled from a distance (remote): remote sensors, remote job, remote control
Hidden away; secluded (remote): remote village
		</theory>
		<name>Frames. Task 1.</name>
		<test>
Fill in the gaps with the following words: far  remote (х2)  distant  far-off
This [answer] village is so out of the way that mail comes only once a week.  #remote
This book bears only a [answer] resemblance to the movie. #distant
Pass through two sets of stop lights and over the bridge. At the [answer] side of the bridge, take a right at the lights onto Memorial Drive. #far
To enjoy this toy you will need a 9V battery for the [answer]control and 6 AA batteries for the car. #remote
I had come across the last remains of a now extinguished dwarf species of emu bird from a [answer] island, Kangaroo Island.  #far-off | far | distant | remote
		</test>
	</unit>
	<unit>
		<theory>
Constructions&amp;Idioms

far:
Can be used with the names of cardinal directions: far West
To an advanced point or stage: a brilliant student who will go far.
Everywhere: far and wide
 Something that is very different from something else: This food is a far cry from what we got in the cafeteria.
distant:
Can express the exact distance: This town is 5 km distant from London
		</theory>
		<name>Constructions&amp;Idioms. Task 2.</name>
		<test>
Fill in the gaps
Instead of returning by way of the Atlantic we made arrangements to cross the Pacific Ocean and voyage via the [answer] East. #far
The hospital in Mbale is a [answer] from what we would expect to find in a UK hospital. #far
We were looking [answer]for the lost diamond ring. #far and wide
One evening, just about sunset, he came to a place among the mountains, more than sixty miles  [answer]   [answer] his home. #distant from
We all need to take some time and focus on something we are eager to learn. Dave - you will do fine and since we all need to learn another language, I know you will [answer]! #go far
		</test>
	</unit>
	<unit>
		<theory>
Word formation
remote:
ADV: remotely
NOUN: remoteness 

distant:
ADV: distantly
NOUN: distance

far:
COMPARATIVE-SUPERLATIVE: far, further/farther, the furthest
NB: further also could be used as ‘next, additional’ (give us a call if you require further information)
		</theory>
		<name>Word formation. Task 3.</name>
		<test>
Fill in the gaps
Intelligent agent software can be downloaded from the Internet or the company's Management and Information System personnel can access the computer [answer](ADV)via the Internet.  #remotely
Giant Pandas The famously rare giant panda occurs only in China, and, according to recent genetic tests, is [answer](ADV) related to the bear. #distantly
Light would have covered the [answer](NOUN) in around 2.4 thousands of a second #distance
Our users would log in [answer](ADV), do their work, and the data transfer took place locally on that server #remotely
For [answer](COMPARATIVE) details please contact us at 077734. #further
Due to the [answer] of Australia, the flight Moscow-Sydney will take 15 hours. #remoteness
		</test>
	</unit>
</all>